Papers of Diane Wakoski circa 1959-1980 (bulk 1959-1978)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VI: Correspondence, additional records, 1960-1980
  - Bell, Marvin, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Bell, Robyn, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Bellamy, Joe David, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Bemis, Kevin, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Benedikt, Michael, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Bennett, Beth, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Bennett, Ken, undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Benson, David, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Benton, William (Bill), undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Berenger, Amanda, undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Berge, Carol, undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Berkeley Poets, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Berman, Cassia, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Berryhill, Michael, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Bertholf, Robert, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Bertolino, James, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Bethel, Gar, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Bialy, Harvey, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Binghamton State University of New York, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Bishop, Elizabeth, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Bishop, Nadean, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Blackburn, Paul, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Blackcock, William, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Blast, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Blau, Rachel, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Blazek, Douglas, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Blue Monday, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Blueridge Travel Ltd, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Bly, Robert, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Boies, Jack, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Bollingen Prize in Poetry of the Yale Library, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Book Lists, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Book Dealers, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Bowers, Orrin, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Bowles, Gloria, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Bowman, David, 1976-April 1977 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Bowman, David, May 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Bradford, Andrea, May 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Brautigan, Richard, undated (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Bread Loaf Writers Conferences, undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Breslin, Paul, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Briskin, Mae, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Bromige, David, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Brooks, Gwendolyn, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Brooks, Roger L, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Broughton, Alan, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Bronderr, Howard, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Brown, Betty, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Brown, Betty, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Steven Ford (Steve), undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Buckley, Christopher (Chris), undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Buckley, John, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Budowski, Edward, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Bukowski, Charles, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Bumpus, Jerry, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Bunge, Nancy, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Burns, Gerald, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Butterworth, Keen, undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Byrd, Sandi, undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - C, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Cafgane, Marcus, undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Carman, Paul, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Callahan, Patrick, undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Caltech, undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Campbell, Joseph, undated (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Carroll, Jonathan, part 1, undated (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Carroll, Jonathan, part 2, undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Carroll, Paul and Gloria, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Carruth, Hayden, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Casey, Crysta, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Cassandra Foundation, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Cassius Clay Press, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Catacalos, Rosemary, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Carwright, Jim, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Cele, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Cervantes, Lorna Dee, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Chester H. Jones Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Chester H. Jones Foundation, part 1, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Chester H. Jones Foundation, part 2, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Chester H. Jones Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Chrisman, Robert, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Ciardi, John, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Clark, L.D. and La Verne H., undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Clewell, David, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Cody’s Books, Inc, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Cohen, Robert David, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Colando, Jim and Cathy, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Colby, Clint, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Coleman, Wanda, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Collectors, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Colorado College, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers (COSMEP), undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - A Commotion of Zebras, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Contests, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Contoski, Victor, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Cooke, Michael G., undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Cooney, Seamus, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines (CCLM), undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Copper Canyon Press, undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Corinth Books, undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Cornis Pop, undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Cotter, Craig, undated (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Cotter, Craig, undated (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Crane, Jill, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Crazy Horse, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Crea, Tony, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Creeley, Robert, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Creeley Session, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Crowell, Charles, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Cuddihy, Michael, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Cullum, Jerry, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Cultural Council Foundation, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - D, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - D’Amboise, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Danziger, Paula, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Davidovicz, Annie, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Davis, Mary, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Defiance, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - DeMaria, Robert, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Den Boer, James, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Deutch, Richard, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Devine, Mary, undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Dhondt, Steve, undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Dickey, James, undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Distinguished Scholar Exchange Program, China, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Diaz-Diocaretz, Myriam, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Doar, Harriet, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Dobb, Sherri, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Domina, Lynn, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Doogan, Margaret B. (Peggy), undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Dorn, Sherry, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Generosity Press/ Dr. Generosity’s, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Doubleday, 1965-1968 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Doubleday, 1969-1973 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Doubleday, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Doubleday, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Doubleday, 1978-1981 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Dow, Philip, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Doyle, Mike, undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Drake, Barbara and Al (Bud), undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Driscoll, Jack, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Ducati, Marilyn, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Duncan, Robert, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Dunn, Stephen, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Dyer, Danny, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - E, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Europe, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Eastern Europe, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Eberhart, Richard, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Edelstein, Mel and Eleanor (Nel); Edelstein, Eleanor: In the Yosemite, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Editor’s Letters: Magazines, Books: A-F, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Editors’ Letters: G-M, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Editors’ Letters: N-P, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Editors’ Letters: Q-W, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Einhorn, Wendy, undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Elswit, Sharon, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - England-Papers, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Enslin, Theodore (Ted), 1962-1963 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Enslin, Theodore (Ted), 1964-1982 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Epstein, Daniel Mark, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Eshleman, Clayton, 1965-1970 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Eshleman, Clayton, 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Eshleman, Clayton, 1973-1975 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Eshleman, Clayton, 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Eshleman, Clayton, 1980-1982 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Eshleman Clayton, 1983-1986 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Everett/Edwards, Inc., undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Everson, William (Brother Antoninus), undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Falleur, Barbara, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Fallon, Tom, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Fagundo, Ana-Maria, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Fan Letters: Undated, part 1 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Fan Letters: Undated, part 2 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Fan Letters: Undated, part 3 (Smith, Susan: Instruments of the Wind) (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Fan Letters, etc, 1967-1971 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - FFan Letters, etc: 1972, part 1 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Fan Letters, etc: 1972, part 2 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Fan Letters, etc: 1973, part 1 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Fan Letters, etc: 1973, part 2 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Fan Letters: 1974, part 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Fan Letters: 1974, part 2 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Fan Letters: 1975, part 1 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Fan Letters: 1975, part 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Fan Letters, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Fan Letters, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Fan Letters, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Fan Letters, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Fan Letters, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Fan Letters, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Fan Letters, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Fan Letters, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Fan Letters, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Fan Letters, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Fan Letters, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - F, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Farrar, Straus and Giroux, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Faulkner, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Fergeson, William, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Ferrier, Carole, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Fiction International, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Field, Edward, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Figueroa, Jose-Angel, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Fiset, Joni, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Fish, Cheryl, undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Fitzgerald, Richard (Rick) and Linda, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Fitzgerald, Richard: Conversations with R.J. Stonehall, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Floras, John, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Fluno, Bob, undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Flynn, George, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Foote, Gary, undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Forche, Carolyn, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Foushee, Sandra, undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Fowler, Theresa, undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Fox, Gregg (See also Fritz, Martha), undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Franks, David: Poems, undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Franks, David, undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Fraser, Kathleen, undated (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Friendly Local Press, undated (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Fritz, Martha (See also Fox, Gregg), undated (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Fullerton Union High School (FUHS), undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Fulbright Awards, 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Furey, Ken, undated (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - G, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Gabriel, Sara M., undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Gale Research Company, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Gangemi, Kenneth (Ken), undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Gardels, Susan, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Garland, Steven C., undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Garmhausen, Jim, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Gaughan, Dennis M., undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Gay, Pamela, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Gean, Karen C., undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Geary, Pat/ Gorlin Debra, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - The George Washington Poems: orders, part 1, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - The George Washington Poems: orders, part 2, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - The George Washington Poems: orders, part 3, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - The George Washington Poems: Orders part 4, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - The George Washington Poems: Orders, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - The George Washington Poems: Advertising, Selling contract, Sales Figures, Review, etc, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Gerber, Dan, undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Gey, Fredric, undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Gilbert, Sandra, undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Gioseffi, Daniela, undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Gitin, David (and Maria), undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Gladysz, Thomas and Hots, Chris, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Goedicke, Patricia, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Gold, Austin, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Good, Jessica, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Goodson, Clint, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Gordon, Bonnie, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Gottfried, Herb, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Goya, Alan, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Great Lakes Colleges Association (GLCA), undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Greenberg, Alvin (Al) and Wendy (Parish) >, undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Greenlee, Jim, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Green River Review, undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Green, Mary K, undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Grolier Book Shop, undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Gross Berry, undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Grossinger, Richard and Lindy (Hough), undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Grossman, Andrew, undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Guard, Michael, undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Guernsey, Bruce H.: Lost Wealth, undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Guggenheim, John Simon: Memorial Foundation, part 1, undated (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, part 2, undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Gunderson, Gwen, undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Gunderson, Keith, undated (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - H, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Hahn, Robert and Nicky, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Hall, Donald, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Hall, Oakley, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Hamandy, Walter and Mary, 1968-1971 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Hamandy, Walter and Mary, 1972-1975 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Hamandy, Walter and Mary, 1976-1979 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Hamandy, Walter and Mary, 1981-1986 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Hammen, Valerie, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Hansman, Gerald: The Skin Walker, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Hantt, Rick, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Hanzlicek, Chuck, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Haravec, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Harmon, Bill, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Harpers’ Bazaar, undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Harriman, John, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Harris, Marguerite, undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Harris, Mark, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Harrison, Jim, undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Hart, Joby and Stephan, undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Hartman, Charles, undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - The Harvard Advocate, undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Harwood, Grace, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Hass, Bob, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Hassan, Ihab, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Hatch, Jim, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - The Hawaii Review, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Hawaii, University of at Manoa, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Hawkes, John, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Haystack, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Healy, Claire, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Hearse, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Heffernan, Bill, undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Heiferman, Marvin, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Hepworth, James R.:, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Hepworth, James R.:, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Hepworth, James R.:, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Hepworth, James R.:, 1981, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Herbert, Rembert, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Herman, M. L., undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Herscoutiz, Marcia, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Heynen, Jim, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Hilberry, Conrad, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Hindley, Norman and Pamela, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Hobbs, J. Kline, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Holst, Spencer, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Hongo, Garrett, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Hope, Eleanor, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Horevitz, Richard P., undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Hoy, Nancy Jo (Jody), undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Hu, Stephen, undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Hudgins, Christopher, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Hudspith, Vickie, undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Huff, Bob, undated (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Humphrey, James, undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Humphrey, Jennifer (Jenny) and Roger Skillings, undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Hunt, Barbara, undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Huntsberry, Bill, undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - I, undated (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - The Ingram Merrill Foundation, undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Kuko Atsumi, undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Illinois Arts Council, undated (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Illuminations, undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Incredible Things, undated (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Ignatow, David, undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Ignatow, David, undated (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Inman, Will, undated (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - International Festival of Poetry, Toronto, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - International Poetry Forum, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Interviews, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - The Iowa Review, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Irvine (University of California, Irvine), undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - J, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Jacobs, Lucky, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Jacobson, Sally, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Janik, Phyllis, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Jeremy, Joseph A., undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Jerome, Judson, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Johns, Jasper, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, J. Chester, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Kirk, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Paul E., undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Jones, Billy, undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Jones, Jeanetta L., undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Joseph, Terri B., undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - K, undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Kalmbach, J., undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Kan, Lilah, undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Kania, Karin, undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Katz, William A. (Bill), undated (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Kaufman, Linda, undated (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Kaufman, Shirley, undated (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Kehl, Richey, undated (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Kelleher, Ann C.:, 1974- July 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Kelleher, Ann C., 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Kelly, Robert, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Kelly, Robert and Joby, 1961-1967 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 5 Kelly, Robert and Joby, 1968-1977 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Kendler, Helene, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy, Joe, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Keuling, Fran, undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Kicknosway, Faye, undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Kilgore, James C., undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Kinnell, Galway, undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Kinter, William, undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Klingaman, Steven, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Kooks, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Koppelman, George, undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Kozlovsky, Dan, undated (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Kraf, Elaine: The Princess of 72nd Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Krehbiel, John Jr., undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Kretchman, Trudy, undated (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Krey, Betty, undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Kriesberg, Hadea, undated (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Kumin, Maxine, undated (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Kuzma, Greg, undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - L, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Laguna Poets, undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Lake Forest College, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Lalic, Ivan. J., undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Lampert, Gerald (Jerry), undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Lane, Ronnie M. (Ron), undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Lang, Nancy, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Lansing, Gerrit, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Lauter, Estrella, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Lawder, Doug, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Laurence (D.H.) Fellowship, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Leaves, Connecticut, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Lee, Steven J., undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Leed, Jacob, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Leiter, Lindarose, undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Lenfest, David, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - The Lenox Arts Center, undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - The Letter Edged in Black Press, Inc., undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Letters to Editors, undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - LeRud, Sandi, undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Levant, Howard, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Levasseur, Richard L., undated (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Levendosky, Charles, undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Levertov, Denise, undated (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Levine, Joan, undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Levinson, James H., undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Levis, Larry, undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Levitt, Mindy, undated (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Lewis, Harry, undated (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Lieberman, Larry, undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Lincoln, Beatrice, undated (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Litvack, Barry, undated (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Livingston, Clare, undated (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Loesch, Karen M., undated (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Logan, John, undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Lordly and Dame, Inc., undated (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Los Angeles, University of California, undated (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Lousiana State University, undated (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Love, Peter, undated (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Low, Denise, undated (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Lurie, Alison, undated (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Lutes, Linda, undated (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Lyndon, Nick, undated (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - M, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - McGarth, Thomas, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - McKernan, Llewellyn, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Macalester College, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Magazines: A-D, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Magazines: E-O, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Magazines: P-Z, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - MacDonald, Ross (Kenneth Millar), undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - MacDonell, Colony, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Mackintosh, Graham, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - MacLow, Jackson and Lezak, Iris, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Madden, David, undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Mailer, Norman, undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Major, Clarence, undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Mandel, Charlotte, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Mannerly, Becky, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - The Mannes College of Music, undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Margolis, Gary, undated (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Marlone, Alan S. and Diane (D. Prima), undated (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Martin, John/ Black Sparrow Press, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1974-1976 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1977-1979 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 10)